# **Max Kless**

Software Engineer

#### Contact

**Address** 

Munich, BY, 81375

E-mail

maxkless.dev@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/max-kless-398530216/

**WWW** 

https://github.com/MaxKless

#### **Skills**

**Angular** 

**Typescript** 

**RXJS & NGRX** 

HTML & CSS

C#

Development Tools (Git, VSCode, etc.)

## Languages

German

Excellent

English

Excellent

Recent computer science graduate that is currently working as a Software Engineer at Intershop Communications AG.

Over three years of experience working with Angular and loving it. Passionate about writing code and always looking to learn. Successfully researched and integrated multiple libraries and frameworks into enterprise software. B.Sc. in Computer Science but far from done educating myself. Love working within a team, collaborating and learning from each other.

#### **Work History**

2020-10 -Current

#### **Software Engineer**

Intershop Communications AG, Jena, TH
Currently member of the Intershop PWA team

- Developing, maintaining and testing a large Angular code base
- Working on open source software: https://github.com/intershop/pwa
- Writing Documentation
- Collaborating as part of a SCRUM Team, refining problems and reviewing code
- Working with a tech stack including Azure, Docker,
   Git, ESLint and Express.js

2018-03 -2020-09

# **Working Student Engineering**

Intershop Communications AG, Jena, TH
Worked in multiple teams learning about and building
enterprise Angular applications.

## **Education**

2016-10 -2020-07

## **Bachelor of Science: Computer Science**

Friedrich-Schiller-Universität - Jena

Thesis topic: Controlling virtual agents in an urban traffic simulation